<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Agreement</string>
    <string name="Agreement">KASPERSKY LAB END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT
IMPORTANT LEGAL NOTICE TO ALL USERS: CAREFULLY READ THE FOLLOWING LEGAL AGREEMENT BEFORE YOU START USING THE SOFTWARE.

BY DOWNLOADING OR USING THE SOFTWARE YOU CONSENT TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO ALL OF THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT, DO NOT DOWNLOAD OR USE THIS SOFTWARE.

1. Definitions
1.1. Software means software for which this Agreement is provided and related materials.
1.2. Rightholder (owner of all rights, whether exclusive or otherwise to the Software) means Kaspersky Lab ZAO, a company incorporated according to the laws of the Russian Federation.
1.3. Computer(s) means hardware, including personal computers, laptops, workstations, personal digital assistants, "smart phones", handheld devices, or other electronic devices for which the Software was designed where the Software will be installed and/or used.
1.4. End User (You/Your) means individual(s) installing or using the Software on their own behalf or who are legally using a copy of the Software; or, if the Software is being downloaded or installed on behalf of an organization, such as an employer, "You" further means the organization for which the Software is downloaded or installed and it is represented hereby that such organization has authorized the person accepting this agreement to do so on its behalf. For purposes hereof the term "organization", without limitation, includes any partnership, limited liability company, corporation, association, joint stock company, trust, joint venture, labor organization, unincorporated organization, or governmental authority.
1.5. Partner(s) means organizations or individual(s) who distribute the Software based on an agreement and license with the Rightholder.
1.6. Windows Store means online store the rightholder of which is the Microsoft Corporation (later Microsoft), is intended for the redistribution of the software applications.
1.7. User Manual means user manual, administrator guide, reference book and related explanatory or other materials.

2. Grant of License
2.1. The Rightholder hereby grants You a non-exclusive license to store, load, install, execute, and display (to “use”) the free of charge Software that will substantially perform within the scope of functionality set forth in the User Manual, subject to agreement to the terms and conditions of this Agreement (the “License”).
2.2. You have the right to use the Software on five (5) of the Computers that are affiliated with your Windows Store account.
2.3. If You modify Your Computer or make changes to other vendors’ software installed on it, You may be required by the Rightholder to repeat installation of the Software.
2.4. Without prejudice to any other remedy in law or in equity that the Rightholder may have, in the event of any breach by You of any of the terms and conditions of this Agreement, the Rightholder shall at any time without notice to You be entitled to terminate this License to use the Software.
2.5. You acknowledge and agree if Microsoft releases a new version of the Windows Store, the terms of the License may be terminated and the Software will be automatically removed from the Computer.

3. Technical Support
3.1. Technical Support is provided by the Rightholder by means of the addition of the information about the working of the software in the Rightholder’s knowledge base. The knowledge base is available at:  http://support.kaspersky.com/metro
3.2. Microsoft will not provide any technical support for the Software.

4. Limitations
4.1. You shall not emulate, clone, rent, lend, lease, sell, modify, decompile, or reverse-engineer the Software or disassemble or create derivative works based on the Software or any portion thereof with the sole exception of a non-waiverable right granted to You by applicable legislation, and you shall not otherwise reduce any part of the Software to human-readable form or transfer the licensed Software, or any subset of the licensed Software, nor permit any third party to do so, except to the extent the foregoing restriction is expressly prohibited by applicable law. Neither the Software’s binary code nor source may be used or reverse-engineered to re-create the program algorithm, which is proprietary. All rights not expressly granted herein are reserved by Rightholder and/or its suppliers, as applicable. Any such unauthorized use of the Software shall result in immediate and automatic termination of this Agreement and the License granted hereunder and may result in criminal and/or civil prosecution against You.

5. Limited Warranty and Disclaimer
5.1. You acknowledge, accept and agree that no software is error-free and You are advised to back up the Computer with the frequency and reliability suitable for You.
5.2. THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND THE RIGHTHOLDER MAKES NO REPRESENTATION AND GIVES NO WARRANTY AS TO ITS USE OR PERFORMANCE. EXCEPT FOR ANY WARRANTY, CONDITION, REPRESENTATION OR TERM THE EXTENT TO WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED BY APPLICABLE LAW. THE RIGHTHOLDER AND ITS PARTNERS MAKE NO WARRANTY, CONDITION, REPRESENTATION, OR TERM (EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, WHETHER BY STATUTE, COMMON LAW, CUSTOM, USAGE OR OTHERWISE) AS TO ANY MATTER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, NON-INFRINGEMENT OF THIRD-PARTY RIGHTS, MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, INTEGRATION, OR APPLICABILITY FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. YOU ASSUME ALL FAULTS, AND THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO PERFORMANCE AND RESPONSIBILITY FOR SELECTING THE SOFTWARE TO ACHIEVE YOUR INTENDED RESULTS, AND FOR THE INSTALLATION OF, USE OF, AND RESULTS OBTAINED FROM THE SOFTWARE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING PROVISIONS, THE RIGHTHOLDER MAKES NO REPRESENTATION AND GIVES NO WARRANTY THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR FREE FROM INTERRUPTIONS OR OTHER FAILURES OR THAT THE SOFTWARE WILL MEET ANY OR ALL OF YOUR REQUIREMENTS WHETHER OR NOT DISCLOSED TO THE RIGHTHOLDER.

6. Exclusion and Limitation of Liability
6.1. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW, IN NO EVENT SHALL THE RIGHTHOLDER OR ITS PARTNERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS OR CONFIDENTIAL OR OTHER INFORMATION, FOR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, FOR LOSS OF PRIVACY, FOR CORRUPTION, DAMAGE AND LOSS OF DATA OR PROGRAMS, FOR FAILURE TO MEET ANY DUTY INCLUDING ANY STATUTORY DUTY, DUTY OF GOOD FAITH OR DUTY OF REASONABLE CARE, FOR NEGLIGENCE, FOR ECONOMIC LOSS, AND FOR ANY OTHER PECUNIARY OR OTHER LOSS WHATSOEVER) ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY RELATED TO THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE SOFTWARE, THE PROVISION OF OR FAILURE TO PROVIDE SUPPORT OR OTHER SERVICES, INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, AND RELATED CONTENT THROUGH THE SOFTWARE OR OTHERWISE ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF THE SOFTWARE, OR OTHERWISE UNDER OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY PROVISION OF THIS AGREEMENT, OR ARISING OUT OF ANY BREACH OF CONTRACT OR ANY TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE, MISREPRESENTATION, ANY STRICT LIABILITY OBLIGATION OR DUTY), OR ANY BREACH OF STATUTORY DUTY, OR ANY BREACH OF WARRANTY OF THE RIGHTHOLDER OR ANY OF ITS PARTNERS, EVEN IF THE RIGHTHOLDER OR ANY PARTNER HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

YOU AGREE THAT IN THE EVENT THE RIGHTHOLDER AND/OR ITS PARTNERS ARE FOUND LIABLE, THE LIABILITY OF THE RIGHTHOLDER AND/OR ITS PARTNERS SHALL BE LIMITED BY THE COSTS OF THE SOFTWARE. IN NO CASE SHALL THE LIABILITY OF THE RIGHTHOLDER AND/OR ITS PARTNERS EXCEED THE FEES PAID FOR THE SOFTWARE TO THE RIGHTHOLDER OR THE PARTNER (AS MAY BE APPLICABLE).

NOTHING IN THIS AGREEMENT EXCLUDES OR LIMITS ANY CLAIM FOR DEATH AND PERSONAL INJURY. FURTHER IN THE EVENT ANY DISCLAIMER, EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION IN THIS AGREEMENT CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED ACCORDING TO APPLICABLE LAW THEN ONLY SUCH DISCLAIMER, EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION SHALL NOT APPLY TO YOU AND YOU CONTINUE TO BE BOUND BY ALL THE REMAINING DISCLAIMERS, EXCLUSIONS AND LIMITATIONS.

7. Intellectual Property Ownership </string>
</resources>
